

HELEN KEELING

Junior Developer

CONTACT

helenlkeeling@gmail.com

On request

www.helenkeeling.co.uk

🏠 Nottingham

EDUCATION

BSC(HONS) INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

2011

2:2

University of Derby

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

Bootstrap

Javascript

PHP

Laravel

Git/Github

SQL Pro

Jira

REFERENCE

On request

ABOUT

Helen is a hardworking, self-motivated individual with over 8 years of experience in the insurance industry.

Helen graduated from the University of Derby in 2011 with a degree in Information Technology, after graduating she took to a career within Insurance. Helen has been at Vasek Insurance/Arthur J. Gallagher & Co since October 2016 and in August 2019 Helen was successful in obtaining her first Junior Developer role.

In her spare time Helen likes to undertake web based courses on PHP and Laravel in addition to maintaining her own website at http://www.helenkeeling.co.uk. Helen can also be found keeping up with the latest game releases.

EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR DEVELOPER

Vasek Insurance/Arthur J. Gallagher & Co. | Aug 2019 - Present

- Undertaking bug fixes and implementing new features on both front and back end of our 6 different websites
- Collaborating with the senior developers on more complex fixes/new features
- Continuing self learning and development via Laracast
- Report work progress via Jira and using Git for version control

HOUSEHOLD ACCOUNT EXECUTIVE

Vasek Insurance/Arthur J. Gallagher & Co. | Oct 2016 - Aug 2019

- Dealing with underwriting queries for household, high net worth, blocks of flats.
- Processing policy cancellations, renewals and mid-term adjustments in line with the underwriting guide.
- Reviewing technical reports.
- Underwriting new business risks
- Dealing with incoming telephone, email and live chat enquiries.
- Placing risks on cover, taking payments and ensuring all paperwork is correct and up to date.

TIER 2 SUBSIDENCE ADVISOR

Crawford & Co. | Oct 2012 - Sept 2016

- Management of personal cases both domestic and commercial, proactively progressing to move them forward.
- Routinely communicating updates to the customer regarding their case.
- Handling complaints for claims in an expedient manner.
- Generating correspondence and third party documentation against claims.
- Analyse and interpret technical reports associated with a claim.
- Recognised by CEO for customer service skills based on customer feedback.
- Received RepairNet award for work with assisting contractors.